(Penny:)I'm saying you and string theory
sound like a relationship,
(Penny:)and I know what it's like
to be in one
(Penny:)and realize it's never gonna
turn out the way you want.
(Sheldon:)I said Leonard, you said no.
(Penny:)I'm talking about other guys.
OK. Well, what do you do?
(Penny:)You have to have the courage
to end the relationship.
(Penny:)You know? Break it off,
shake hands, walk away.
(Sheldon:)I don't know if I can do that.
(Penny:)I know it's hard, honey,
but in the end, that's how you grow.
(Leonard:)Penny, have you seen
my good inhaler?
(Penny:)Break it off,
shake hands, walk away.
Hey, how's dating two women going'?
(Raj:)Um, kind of hit a bump.
(Raj:)When I was honest and told Emily
(Raj:)she wasn't the only person
I was seeing, it went great.
(Raj:)So I tried the same thing with Lucy.
(Howard:)-And?
-She had mixed feelings.